<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Rochester 2600</title>
    <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Rochester 2600</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.rochester2600.com/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 02/02/2018 Spectre Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/02-02-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/02-02-2018/</guid>
      <description>
Join us this month for a exploration of power lifting while we take a look at implications of nostril hair on anger and mobile cybers . Presentations this months include:
 Antitree: This month in infosec JRWR: Point of Shit System Pee: Autohate DNSSEC  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 01/05/2017 New Year 2018 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/01-06-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/01-06-2018/</guid>
      <description>
Attending a 2600 meeting this month means you will see a speed round about hacking much as our presenters share their knoweldge about a deeply sad comparison between angels and SDR . YOLO:
 All: This month in infosec TBD  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 12/01/2017 Roo Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-01-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-01-2017/</guid>
      <description>
NOTE: This month will be at RIT&amp;rsquo;s GCCIS building room 1400. That&amp;rsquo;s Building 070 GOL-1400. You can park in the lot closest to the building without a permit. See RIT Parking Page for more specific information.
Wow. Big month. It&amp;rsquo;ll be a a very serious discussion about the information divide as we complain about problems of cryptography and headphones . I appologize in advance for the following talks:
 Antitree: This month in infosec Joe: SSH&amp;rsquo;ing on your parade Antitree: Reports from the Radical Left Antitree: Put this in your pip and smoke it  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 11/03/2017 Rad Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-03-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-03-2017/</guid>
      <description>
Welp. Time for another meeting. Come on down this month and see a slap in the face of security while we watch a parasitic gap construction. Thomas and Rust. Anyways, here&amp;rsquo;s the list of talks:
 Antitree: This month in infosec Joe: SSH&amp;rsquo;ing on your parade Antitree: Tor Updates for 2049  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 10/06/2017 Thermite Day Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-6-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-6-2017/</guid>
      <description>
The First Friday 2600 meeting will be a time for awkward lack of eye contact as we chat about the state of infosec and its negative affect on the economy and talk about an oversimplified comparative anlaysis of mobile cybers and Washington . I appologize in advance for the following talks:
 Someone: This month in infosec Dr. Robo Alex: Let&amp;rsquo;s get Quantum Physical Cowboy Joe: SSHH&amp;hellip; don&amp;rsquo;t tell anyone yet  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 09/01/2017 Mayweather Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/08-27-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/08-27-2017/</guid>
      <description>
For thos interested, the meeting this month is a slap in the face of dissapointment while we open up the forums to discuss a deeply sad comparison between Brian and nose hair . Here are the actual talks this month:
 Someone: This month in infosec Some Other guy: Look at me! Tizen! Sum Guy: Let&amp;rsquo;s get Quantum Physical  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 08/04/2017 Antisec Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/07-24-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/07-24-2017/</guid>
      <description>
Get ready for a trist into unmitigated hate while we watch a size comparison of lean beef and pseudoscience . Presentations this months include:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec TheQuantumJoeTesta: SSHit and FTPee AntiTree: For your eyes only GuestSpeaker: Look, I did something  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 7/7/2017 Spongebob Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/07-07-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/07-07-2017/</guid>
      <description>
Rochester 2600 is going to devote some time to be a celebration of the state of infosec while we sip our drinks and look at a deeply sad comparison between Brian and demons . Here are the actual talks this month:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Pee: DNSSEC and Rage Alex: Taking The Greenlight When You&amp;rsquo;re Not Given It InvestigatorChic: DEFCON 25 Preview  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 06/02/2017 RIT Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/06-02-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/06-02-2017/</guid>
      <description>UPDATE: Rochester 2600 will be hosted at RIT this month.
Building 70 (GCCIS), Room 2500 RIT, &amp;quot;Rochester&amp;quot;, NY  Parking is permitted anytime after 6pm in front of the building. (Same as where BSidesROC was)
Rochester 2600 is going to devote some time to be a deep discussion of the information divide while we listen to implications of nostril hair on a depressed fourth grader and Jason&amp;rsquo;s lost soul .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 05/05/2017 onion Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-5-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-5-2017/</guid>
      <description>
2600 this month is a giant pile of prestigue as we appologize for common methods of destroying Bitcoin and T.O.R. . YOLO:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec AntiTree: Tor Browser Bundle vs Firefox  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 4/7/2017 BSidesROC Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/04-07-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/04-07-2017/</guid>
      <description>
Get ready for a metric fuck-ton of pride and prejudice as we put our ear to the ground about a corpus of utterance tokens between hate and fear . This will be done via presentations below:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 3/3/2017 Amusing Ourselves To Death Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/03-03-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/03-03-2017/</guid>
      <description>
Join us this month for a eye-brow raising thought exercise about Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s hair throughout our meditation on a deeply sad comparison between DEFCON and Shmoocon . Agenda below:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec CowboyJoe: NIST, Elliptical Curves, and Trust AntiTree: The 2600 Industrial Intelligence Machine JustBill: Infrastructure Improvements at Interlock AntiTree: Identifying vulnerabilities in the tor network and tools  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 2/3/2017 This Is Fine Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/02-03-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/02-03-2017/</guid>
      <description>The First Friday 2600 meeting will be a time for us all to think about happiness in spite of our presenters disclosing their feelings on a sumo wrestle match between Bitcoin and power hungry dwarves . Well here it is:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec TBD: Other presentations  (sarcastically generated by 2600gen bot)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 1/6/2017 33C3 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/01-07-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/01-07-2017/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for a hilarious examination of our feelings as we explore problems of power hungry dwarves and MongoDB . Here&amp;rsquo;s what you can expect:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Alex: What you can get into by saying you&amp;rsquo;re a journalist AntiTree: Android 7.1 Security AntiTree,Alex: Teufelsberg NSA Field Station AntiTree: Web Api Demo Jason: Nothing as always.  (sarcastically generated by 2600gen bot)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 12/2/2016 Barret Brown Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-2-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-2-2016/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for a time for awkward lack of eye contact as we chat about mother/daughter relationships as we put in just the tip about a size comparison of balls and MongoDB . Gah. Whatever. Talks below:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec AntiTree: Copperhead OS: Android With Security Alex: Image Processing NSFW Style Joe: TBA  (sarcastically generated by 2600gen bot)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 11/4/2016 Y U No Talks Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-4-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-4-2016/</guid>
      <description>Attending a 2600 meeting this month means you will see a deep dive into monkeys and their relationships much as our presenters share their knoweldge about problems of balls and a depressed fourth grader . This will be done via presentations below:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec AntiTree: This month in legal threats  (sarcastically generated by 2600gen bot)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 10/7/2016 Donald Trump Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-7-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-7-2016/</guid>
      <description>The First Friday 2600 meeting will be a hilarious examination of the separation of church and state while we sip our drinks and look at which melts faster between two fluffy pillows and Andrew. Gah. Whatever. Talks below:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Jason: DEVOPs for dummies or how I learned to stop worrying about infosec and just script things for developers AntiTree: Tales Of Czech Support AntiTree: Android 7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 9/2/2016 Yawning Pidgeon Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/9-2-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/9-2-2016/</guid>
      <description>
For thos interested, the meeting this month is a hilarious examination of our feelings as we dive head first into a corpus of utterance tokens upon which conformity has been defined by the paired utterance test. Presentations this months include:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec AntiTree: ZCash: Shitcoin or Shitcoin? Cowboi Joe: Look what I can do with Ethereum  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 8/5/2016: DEFCON 24 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/8-5-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/8-5-2016/</guid>
      <description>
Get ready for a slap in the face of pride and prejudice while we open up the forums to discuss a parasitic gap construction. Here is an agenda for the night:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Cowboi Joe: Ethereum is still a thing? Alex: The State Of Home Automation AntiTree: WiFi: It still sucks  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 7/1/2016: Autogenerated Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/7-1-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/7-1-2016/</guid>
      <description>
Join us this month for a deep dive into anonymity much as our presenters share their knoweldge about a stipulation to place the constructions into these various categories. I appologize in advance for the following talks:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Cowboi Joe: TheDAO of Ethereum  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 6/3/2016: Something Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/6-3-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/6-3-2016/</guid>
      <description>
Join us to beat the heat. We are sorry to say that this month we will actualy have interesting presentations.
Presentations:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Jynik: Mouse Jacking via RF AntiTree: Docker Security  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 5/6/2016: Cryptoparty Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-6-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-6-2016/</guid>
      <description>This will be Rochester 2600&amp;rsquo;s first (and maybe only) cryptoparty. A Cryptoparty is a hands on workshop that teaches anyone about important security and cryptography tools you can use to protect yourself. There will be a focus this time around on OpenPGP/GPG and the new operating systems QubesOS and SubgraphOS.
What you need to participate:
 Laptop ideally with Linux installed on it Copy of your OpenPGP fingerprint Proof of identity  What you need to attend:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 4/1/2016: April Fools Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/4-1-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/4-1-2016/</guid>
      <description>
There will be a meeting on 4&amp;frasl;1. It&amp;rsquo;s not an april fools joke but it is a joke, and it&amp;rsquo;s in April. This will be a hands on introduction to smart cards and OpenPGP along with our standard presentations.
Presentations:
 AntiTree: This month in infosec Pee &amp;amp; Antitree: SmartCards, Nitrokeys, and how to store them in your butt. TheStroudCloud: Deep Dive into Docker  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 3/4/2016: Unknown Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/3-4-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/3-4-2016/</guid>
      <description>
There will be a meeting on 3&amp;frasl;4. Of what, we do not know. Who will be there we do not know. Will there be a presentation? Unknown.
Presentations:
 TBD TBA IDK  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 2/5/2016: Black Elephant Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/2-5-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/2-5-2016/</guid>
      <description>
Black Elephant is our monthly holiday party where attendees come in an exchange the most horrible gifts possible. Please note this is not for the faint of heart. We will also have our monthly presentations along-side the gift exchange. Exchange is optional but again, be warned.
Presentations:
 G13: Sniffing your butt AntiTree: Shamir&amp;rsquo;s Secrets Algorythm: Nothing as always CowBoiJoe: &amp;ldquo;I can&amp;rsquo;t tell you because I would have to kill you&amp;rdquo; x56: Something To Disclose All: Black Elephant Gift Sharing  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 1/1/2016: Cancelled</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/1-1-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/1-1-2016/</guid>
      <description>There will be no meeting this month an account of terrorism.. or because no one is going to be around. Join us next month for another action packed adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 12/4/2015: Season Affected eDition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-4-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/12-4-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Join us for a S.A.D. meeting where we will discuss all of our sadness. Seasonal Affected eDition will also discuss some security related topics like the previous month. If you are sad or have SAD or took some Sad, make sure you call someone besides us, we can&amp;rsquo;t help.
 antitree: This month in security and dogs /dev/urand: 5err challenge v2: bigger and sadder a1g0ry7hm: Freenet makes us sad g13: Something, maybe, depending, on how much Sad he took  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 11/6/2015: Back To The Future Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-6-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/11-6-2015/</guid>
      <description>
We now live so far in the future that we don&amp;rsquo;t need roads. Join us as we fuel our minds with garbage at another 2600 meeting. (make sure you bring your hoverboards, self-lacing shoes, and metal hats!)
 antitree: This month in infosec /dev/urand: 5err challenge a1g0ry7hm: inane babbling  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 10/2/2015 Herdy Gurdy Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/10-2-2015/</guid>
      <description>
The boys are back in town, the boys are back in town&amp;hellip; from DEFCON. Join us for another installment of 2600. Topics range from Canary Tokens and web security to what to do with 30 pounds of thermite.
 AntiTree: This Month in Infosec History AHoll: TBA AntiTree: Canary Tokens AntiTree: Fun With Fiverr AntiTree: Twitter Api Silliness aLgoRYthm: JWT (and maybe a teeny bit on HTTP/2)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 9/4/2015 Yup Edtion</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/9-4-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/9-4-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Meeting this month. Yup.
 Algorythm: TBA Alex: Important things of the month  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 8/7/2015 Jeep Stunt Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/8-7-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/8-7-2015/</guid>
      <description>
This month will be focuse on Jeep stunting. Everyone brings a Jeep that they bought, leased, or stolen and we will take turns driving it at 70 MPH until someone hacks us from Las Vegas. Other presentations include:
 AntiTree: Months in review AntiTree: Hacked Team Overview Algorythm: List of things that you&amp;rsquo;re missing at DEFCON  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 7/3/2015 Lemonade Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/7-3-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/7-3-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Join us for Rochester 2600: Lemonade Edition. This meeting will pay tribute to all things lemonade related including revolve, eyeliner, and cause. This month&amp;rsquo;s talks include:
 AntiTree: Month in review AntiTree: How To Hack: Those commands I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you about AntiTree: Attacks via Python DNS server AntiTree: Sans Bullshit Cyber Sans  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 6/5/2015 Beard Swimming Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/6-5-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/6-5-2015/</guid>
      <description>
The month will entail testing out the new swim gear to cut down on the drag of your beard when you&amp;rsquo;re swimming. We&amp;rsquo;ll also talk about InfoSec stuff, probably.
 AntiTree: Months in review Alex: Look at my Arduino Cell Phone AntiTree: USBKill AntiTree: BitCoin MultiSig AntiTree: BTCJam AntiTree: Astoria tor client AntiTree: OPSView at Interlock AntiTree: SpiderFoot, another recon system AntiTree: Introduction to NFMI Vince: TBA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 5/1/2015 Worst Of Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-1-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/5-1-2015/</guid>
      <description>
This month will be a best-of/worst-of Rochester 2600. Presenters will bring out updates to some of our favorite talks. 2600 welcomes all our new friends from BSidesROC.
 AntiTree: Months in review AntiTree: Lisbeth vs Bond: Corporate Spying JustBill: Ubiquity Wireless at Interlock Cowboijoe: TBA Algorythm: TBA Andrew: TBA  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 4/3/2015 BSidesROC 2015 Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/4-3-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/4-3-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Rochester 2600, the main organizer of Security B-SidesROC, we be having their last meeting before the event. Join us while we work on our projects, share random presentations, and discuss logistics of the event. All are welcome but this will not be a normal 2600 meeting
 Algorythm: Postman AntiTree: Months in review AntiTree: Selenium and PhantomJS All: BSidesROC planning  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 3/6/2015 Black Elephant Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/3-6-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/3-6-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Now that the holidays are over, it&amp;rsquo;s time to have our own holiday event, 2600 style. Join us for a black elephant event of random gift exchange. Those participating should bring a random, useless gift that will be forced upon attendees. Particpation is not recommended.
 AntiTree: Months in review AntiTree: NSA and VPNs Jynik: YateBTS AntiSeth: The Sony Hacks Timeline CowboiJoe: Social Engineering a Car All: Black Elephant Exchange  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 2/6/2015 Random Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/2-6-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/2-6-2015/</guid>
      <description>Join us this month for a completely random edition of 2600. There are no planned presentations this month and people are free to hang out, chat, and share what you&amp;rsquo;re working on. Or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting 1/2/2015 Santa Claus Is Still Drunk Edition</title>
      <link>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/1-2-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.rochester2600.com/home/1-2-2015/</guid>
      <description>
Bring in the new years with 2600 as we will meet up to discuss why we are all still wearing Santa outfits. Nothing says &amp;ldquo;screw it&amp;rdquo; more than refusing to take off your rum covered Saint Nick costume.
 Jason: Monthly summary of infosec events TBA  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>